https://americantoursandtravel.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy | American Tours & TravelPrivacy Policy | American Tours & Travel
FacebookTwitterCALL TO BOOK TODAY!
407-351-2500Music GroupsMarching BandsOrchestra BandJazz BandsChoir GroupsView MoreAll American Music FestivalDisney Candlelight ProcessionalDisney Performing Arts OnStageFestival DisneyOrlandoFest at the Universal Orlando ResortSTARS Performance ProgramSeaWorldDance GroupsClass TripsCruise TravelGroup TripsClass TripsAuxiliary TeamsSports TeamsEducational ToursChurch GroupsCruise TravelDance GroupsMusic GroupsDestinationsAll American Music FestivalAtlantaChicagoDallasDisney WorldGatlinburgHawaiiLos AngelesNew OrleansNew York CityOrlando, FloridaSan-AntonioSeaWorldSt. LouisTorontoUniversal Orlando ResortWashington D.C.More DestinationsExplorePhoto GalleryAbout UsWhat’s New?FAQsTestimonialsOur ServicesWhy We CanCancellation Policies for Land & Air Travel Search
Menu
Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home / Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy – American Tours and TravelsThe ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL policy is to protect and respect the privacy of our users.ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL agrees to exercise reasonable precautions to maintain the confidentiality of information provided by you in connection with accessing this web site. ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL does not collect personal information about individuals from this Site except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals and will not sell, rent, or trade personal information about our users to any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL may disclose personal information in special cases: (1) when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with (either intentionally or unintentionally) ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL’s rights or property; (2) when, after good faith research, we believe that the law requires it; (3) to ALL-AMERICAN TOURS & TRAVEL’s sales and marketing personnel and its suppliers, business partners, regional managers and/or sales representatives as necessary to provide service or information to you that you have requested; and (4) in situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person.When you give us your personal or corporate information (e.g. name, address, phone, fax, e-mail, etc.), we will not sell, trade, or give this information to any third party. Your personal information will only be used to improve our relationship with and the services provided to you.PagesAbout AMTTAbout Our TeamAbout UsAll American Music FestivalAll American Music Festival InquiryAtlantaAuxiliary TeamsCancellation Policies for Land & Air TravelChicagoChoir GroupsChurch GroupsClass TripsCommunity RelationsConsultation RequestContact UsCruise TravelDallasDance GroupsDestinationsDisney Candlelight ProcessionalDisney Performing Arts OnStageDisney WorldDisney Youth Education SeriesEducational ToursEventsFAQsFestival DisneyGatlinburgGroup TripsHawaiiHow to PickImportant Air TravelImportant Industry AffiliationsIndustry AffiliationsJazz BandsLos AngelesMarching BandsMeet Our TeamMeet Our TeamMore DestinationsMore Fun. Less MoneyMusic GroupsNew OrleansNew York CityOrchestra BandOrlando, FloridaOrlandoFest at the Universal Orlando ResortOur GuaranteeOur GuaranteeOur ServicesPackagesPhoto GalleryPhoto GalleryPrivacy PolicyRequest A BrochureRequest Our SecretsRNAV AtlantaRNAV AuxiliaryRNAV AuxiliaryRNAV ChicagoRNAV Class TripsRNAV GatlinburgRNAV HawaiiRNAV Los AngelesRNAV Main OrlandoRNAV Music GroupsRNAV New OrleansRNAV NYCRNAV Orlando PerformanceRNAV San AntonioRNAV TorontoRNAV WashingtonRNAV Washington CopySan-antonioSave Money on Group TravelSeaWorldSign Up For Our NewsletterSports TeamsSt. LouisSTARS Performance ProgramStart PlanningStart Planning Your Student Group Trip NowStudent Group TravelStudent TripsTestimonialsThank youTorontoTravel Policies & ProceduresUniversal Mardi Gras ParadeUniversal Studios Grad BashWashington D.C.What Makes Disney EventsWhat’s NewWhat’s New?Why We CanWorld’s Fastest Drummer CompetitionWorldwide Student Group TravelCategoriesBand TripsClass TripsCompany NewsDance Group TravelFrontpage ArticleImagesNewsStudent Group TravelUncategorizedArchiveJanuary 2016March 2013January 2013November 2012September 2012August 2012July 2012June 2012May 2012February 2012January 2012December 2011September 2011August 2011March 2011February 2011January 2011December 2010August 2010May 2010March 2009Travel AssistanceOur ServicesPhoto GalleryTestimonialsDestinationsGroup TripsEducational ToursCruise TravelWhy We CanPagesAbout AMTTAbout Our TeamAbout UsAll American Music FestivalAll American Music Festival InquiryAtlantaAuxiliary TeamsCancellation Policies for Land & Air TravelChicagoChoir GroupsChurch GroupsClass TripsCommunity RelationsConsultation RequestContact UsCruise TravelDallasDance GroupsDestinationsDisney Candlelight ProcessionalDisney Performing Arts OnStageDisney WorldDisney Youth Education SeriesEducational ToursEventsFAQsFestival DisneyGatlinburgGroup TripsHawaiiHow to PickImportant Air TravelImportant Industry AffiliationsIndustry AffiliationsJazz BandsLos AngelesMarching BandsMeet Our TeamMeet Our TeamMore DestinationsMore Fun. Less MoneyMusic GroupsNew OrleansNew York CityOrchestra BandOrlando, FloridaOrlandoFest at the Universal Orlando ResortOur GuaranteeOur GuaranteeOur ServicesPackagesPhoto GalleryPhoto GalleryPrivacy PolicyRequest A BrochureRequest Our SecretsRNAV AtlantaRNAV AuxiliaryRNAV AuxiliaryRNAV ChicagoRNAV Class TripsRNAV GatlinburgRNAV HawaiiRNAV Los AngelesRNAV Main OrlandoRNAV Music GroupsRNAV New OrleansRNAV NYCRNAV Orlando PerformanceRNAV San AntonioRNAV TorontoRNAV WashingtonRNAV Washington CopySan-antonioSave Money on Group TravelSeaWorldSign Up For Our NewsletterSports TeamsSt. LouisSTARS Performance ProgramStart PlanningStart Planning Your Student Group Trip NowStudent Group TravelStudent TripsTestimonialsThank youTorontoTravel Policies & ProceduresUniversal Mardi Gras ParadeUniversal Studios Grad BashWashington D.C.What Makes Disney EventsWhat’s NewWhat’s New?Why We CanWorld’s Fastest Drummer CompetitionWorldwide Student Group TravelCategoriesBand TripsClass TripsCompany NewsDance Group TravelFrontpage ArticleImagesNewsStudent Group TravelUncategorizedArchiveJanuary 2016March 2013January 2013November 2012September 2012August 2012July 2012June 2012May 2012February 2012January 2012December 2011September 2011August 2011March 2011February 2011January 2011December 2010August 2010May 2010March 20097061 Grand National Drive, Suite #126, Orlando, FL. 32819 Phone 407-351-2500 fax 407-352-2962 © Copyright
- American Tours & TravelFacebookTwitterAbout UsOur GuaranteeContact UsFAQsPrivacy PolicyCancellation Policies
Inquiry FormYour NameNo. of TravelersDestinationOrlando, FloridaUniversal StudiosDisney WorldSeaWorldGroup TypeMusic GroupDance GroupClass TripPhoneEmail MessagePhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Scroll to top
